Yes please.
It's true, but that's a weird song.
The chorus is kind of like that, but it's catchy,
I don't know what to make of it.
It's like I'm making it up as I go along.
Oh, really?
Suddenly, it's like...
It totally ignores the conventional wisdom of music codes.
Okay.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Please do.
Oh, there's more?
Yes.
I drink a lot.
Wow!
Is it amazing?
You must drink it!
500 ml in one gulp?
Oh my God!
Isn't he cool?
You look like a fighter.
I drank a little too much.
He's staring at you right now.
Thank you very much.
The fight has begun, and it's going to happen right now.
I'm so hungry I'm having a hard time... so I'm going to hold a water-drinking contest... a contest... for this week.
I'm Rico Ueda of the Nunchaku Shoujo-tai, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
Let's go, we're the Nullified Girl Squad!
We're the Nullified Girl Squad! Nice to meet you. You remember me.
Perfect.
How's it going?
I've been having a lot of fun at my part-time job this week, and I'm surprised there isn't a script.
I'm sorry, I thought you were doing free talk.
I thought it was a free talk.
We're given a script where we're not allowed to make a single mistake.
I've been reading it for two days before going to bed. You can do it in two days? I'll do it a week in advance.
Not yet, not yet. I skip most of the default parts.
I skip most of the default parts.
I'll be broadcasting live... and we'll keep it going... and going... and going... and going... and going... and going... and going... and going... and going... and going...
DARIKO!
I've decided!
Loudly!
By the way, it was announced officially.
Dariko?
What's that? Someone guessed it. Wow!
We said "Dariko" so loudly, they must've heard us.
You were talking to the Japanese? Yes, I think they could hear us if they were in Yokohama.
So you're saying that people in Yokohama got it right? Yes, everyone in the area.
I'm embarrassed that you asked me that. It's quite a spoiler.
The people who are watching the show right now are up there too.
I'm Dariko, but it's easy to make my voice really loud.
Or maybe it's just as it is. Or maybe it's not.
Everyone, please stand in front of the TV right now.
So, just in case... let's do the experiment.
DARIKO!
It's big! It's big!
But it's easy to say, isn't it?
If you say so, I'll figure it out. If you say so, I guess I'll just have to figure it out.
Hi, I'm DARIKO.
There are a lot of female pin-up comedians these days.
They didn't really accept me by name.
We'll let the recording go on without that.
Yes, sir! That's all for now.
Every time I think about it...
Friday comes too soon!
It's crazy! Already Friday! Already Friday! Well, well, well, well, how was your week? This week has flown by in a blink of an eye, but it has gone by so fast!
It went by so fast, and it was so great, thanks to DynaBytes!
Thanks to Dynavite! Oh, yeah! I'm glad to hear that, but...
I mean, you know, in show business, people often go to Tokyo or other places like Osaka or Fukuoka.
I think it's good to stay in Fukuoka, right?
I'd like to be based in Fukuoka or Kyushu, but I'm not sure if they can match the convenience of Tokyo or Osaka.
Well, I don't know... I don't know... To be honest, there are some things.
It's true that Tokyo is also really great, but only a part of it.
Yes, that's right.
Even in Tokyo, there are places where things are more laid back.
Machida, for example. I live in Machida myself, but it's pretty rural.
It's a nice place, though.
I live in Mitaka too. It's right next to Kichijoji.
It's a gorgeous town, right next to Kichijoji.
It's so gorgeous, and then suddenly, from Mitaka station, it's like...
So many people? That's right. That's the border.
And my station is right next to Musashisakai station.
Musashisakai Toko is like Kokubunji.
Kokubunji suddenly became cute.
The west side of Tokyo is a bit like the center of Fukuoka.
It's laid back. You feel like you're back in Fukuoka.
It's like... It's like...
What is it? What's with the bop-bop? When I go home...
Grandma and grandpa don't say that.
They say batten-batten. That's standard Japanese, right?
Yes, it's in the Hakata dialect, like "What are you doing?
Scary, scary!
Can I hear that one more time?
What are you doing?
We're recording. Great. We're recording.
Rumor has it Kyushu's dialect is the best... spoken by girls.
I agree, from a men's point of view, Kansai dialect is fine and all, but Kyushu's dialect is so much better.
It's great.
He says he likes you.
Can I say it one more time? Translate "I like you" for me.
Translate? I meant you.
It's about you, Suisuto.
But listen to me... we don't use "yo" in the reality of Kuroiwa's misfortune.
What? In real life? Oh no!
Like, "I like you" or "I love you"? You don't say "Toto"?
I say "Toto", but I don't say "I like you".
You're lying! Of course not.
Depends on the region. - Depends on the region?
There are some areas where there are about 4 different dialects, but basically you don't say much?
Basically, they don't say so much.
I think it's going to become more and more homogeneous.
That's right.
I don't want them to stop.
We need it to keep it. We Kanto people need it.
Then get signatures from the Kanto side.
I'm sure we'll get it soon. I'll submit it to Mr. Fukuoka. I'm sure we'll get them soon. I'll submit them to Mr. Fukuoka.
Millions of signatures will be gathered.
I'd like to see you actively use the idea of tasting it. I hope so. I would like to ask you to do so. Let's use it.
That's amazing. You just had an attack, didn't you? I was so nervous that my heart might have stopped for a moment. Especially since we are not accustomed to hearing such things. We are not used to hearing such things, so we were surprised. They are all speaking in standard Japanese.
We are speaking only in standard Japanese.
I'm the most familiar with it.
Especially, I think I speak the most, huh? I mean, in our everyday situations,
For example, when we go to Hakata or Fukuoka for fun or for work, we are prepared to some extent,
I guess it's just like that, people talk like this when they go out to bars or bars.
For example, at work or with friends,
For example, you know, I'm from Fukuoka, and we usually talk like normal people. Suddenly, when I call him on his cell phone, he says "toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot. Wow!
They were always saying such distant things. I was so surprised. That's what makes a big impact on me.
I was envious of him, like, "Wow, there's a world just for him.
It's like a hidden Hakata dialect.
We say "shokuberi," which means "to try to eat," which is something we also use in our daily lives.
We say "shokuberi" when we want to try to eat. Eat, eat, eat.
Even insects? Eat, eat, eat.
Amazing. That's great dialect.
I ate a lot of food, didn't I?
That's great.
Basically, it's like, "Oh, well..."?
That's right.
It's like a dialect.
I like it.
I really like it.
Born in Tokyo.
It's true, that's why we feel a little sad.
That's right.
Even in comments. Comment.
Waterworks Preservation Committee, I can prove it!
Oh let's make it, by all means.
We're already getting together.
It's already gathering like crazy.
Maybe even the Kanto region and this neighborhood will gather soon.
Yes, that's right.
People in Fukuoka don't really feel it.
That's right.
Well, it doesn't matter.
You might say, "Thank God! They might say, "Thank God!
We're dreaming about it. Fukuoka dialect.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't know, Hakata...
I can't help but think that woman on the street crest, the one on the lookup, is the one who's taking the water bottles and saying... That's right.
A woman in a scary kimono. It's just an imaginary image.
So, let's start today...
Well, it's the second half of October. They say it's early.
Today is October 27th.
It is the day of the new world record, which was set in 1931, the 6th year of the Showa era.
In 1931, there was an athletic meet in Japan. There, Japan's first new world record was set.
Mr. Nambu's long jump was 7m98, and Mr. Oda's triple jump was 15m58, both world records at that time.
By the way, from 1931 to the present day, the current world record for the long jump is 8m95m.
The triple jump is 18m29.
But don't you think it's a little less than that?
That's what's amazing.
It's 1931... with the evolution of spikes and clothes... it's amazing that I remember this... this Japanese man's leaf jumping...
I think it's amazing that Japanese people have such a good memory of leaf jumping.
I've never done the triple jump, but when I tried it, I realized it's not only world-class, it's world-class.
I see. I see.
There are people who don't realize that they just don't have the talent.
But you know, 100m, you're no match for Westerners... or foreigners, for that matter.
Because their skeletons are different from ours.
So, Japanese can't compete in power sports, so we have to compete in longer distances, or in the long jump, which requires a little bit more skill.
If we were allowed to fly freely, without that restriction, I think we'd all be able to fly very fast.
I think people would be able to keep it under control because of that.
But if they could fly like that with power, it would be amazing!
It's amazing, isn't it? They're just on the edge.
The same is true of the 3-dan, you know, with the fouls and such.
Without that, it would be very difficult because of the rules.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well...
So, let's see what else you have to say.
Let's see... a letter from a frequent contributor to this program, a guy named "Night Commuter Express".
There's a guy who often writes to this show... and he probably loves trains.
He says he drove a real train for the first time, and there's a place that lets you ride it.
Of course, I think it was in a place where there were no passengers and they were doing some kind of inspection.
Well...
Master! Yes, sir! Brother Sarpong!
Yes, sir! Good evening!
Good evening!
Good evening.
A train starter is an electric train starter, you know, the one with the...
You see this on the train?
It's a kind of electric train with this or that attached to it.
It's a diesel-powered car, and it can move by itself even if there's nothing to start it.
They let me try it out.
I got to experience it for the first time... and he sent me some great pictures of his commute at night...
I heard that real trains are very difficult to make.
The real thing is implemented... like a law of completion. The real thing is the implementation, you know, the rule of completion kind of thing.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, that's great! It's so good!
I think this is originally a track car, but you can see the tension on his face. He looks like he's about to drive!
I'm so excited! I can't get enough of it!
And when he actually drives
He's going to let me drive like this!
Wow, it's so cool!
Well...
Good, good, good, good...
Oh, it's good!
Good!
Yum! Yum! Good!
I wonder why people in the railroad industry talk like that in their internal broadcasts?
The sound is really loud, like a rattling sound.
But, I guess a nasal voice is the best.
Aaah! They want us to hear it!
I've heard it most somewhere.
He's totally drunk on himself...
Too much!
First time this year!
The first time this year...
Are you drunk?
I'm drunk, I'm drunk, I'm drunk, I'm drunk, I'm drunk, I'm drunk.
Next stop: Shinjuku, Shinjuku...
You're drunk!
Thank you for taking the bullet train today!
I don't know... but it's nice...
This is an experience of a lifetime! It's a dream, isn't it?
Especially for boys, if there are 100 boys, about 80 of them like trains.
Why do boys like trains so much? Maybe because they like driving. Why do boys like cars so much?
I like cars too... and I don't know if I'm instinctively attracted to girls.
There are a lot of girls who like trains, but I don't think I've ever been attracted to them.
I don't think I've ever been attracted to cars or anything like that.
I did get a driver's license. A regular driver's license! That's great!
I just thought it would be convenient.
Just because you can get a license doesn't mean you should get a license
Most of them don't have a license. Well, there are some who can't because of their age.
I also had the Corona disaster when I was in college, so I didn't have many classes that were easy to take.
I really didn't want to come back to the school at that time
I really didn't want to ever come back here again.
I still want to go. You liked driving school?
What? Was it that nice?
I always wanted to go to driving school. I wasn't afraid of getting into an accident.
And they brake for you. The course in there...
I don't remember it... but there were hills like this.
There was a S curve...
Blanco... there was a blanco...
Rumor has it that the population is decreasing and the driving schools are in trouble.
No one wants to get a driver's license. People nowadays don't care about cars.
When we were kids, we were the first to get a driver's license, so when our 18th birthday rolled around...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
When you turned 16, you had to get a motorcycle first, and then at 18 you could get a regular license.
But that's not the case now, so in the old days... well, I'm just saying...
I went to a particularly scary driving school where the instructors would suddenly start wearing a perm.
I have that image. I know, I know.
You didn't see him. What were you doing?
I'm glad you're here... but I want you to graduate.
We'll never come back. It's just the two of us.
That's awkward. That's awkward. I don't like it.
Shut up and draw a picture or something. It's not a picture.
Maybe he's sketching.
I've seen it a million times. He won't say anything.
I'm sick of it.
I want to show you something... to everyone.
What do you think?
How's it going?
Oh, that's great.
I don't know much about "screentime," so I'm not used to it.
I'm not used to it. I've got the save seal up and running.
If you could just close it with something like that...
I'm sure the people would be satisfied.
They'll cheer.
What do you think of the "Suitot" and the "Hakata-ben"?
What do they remind you of?
I wonder.
Women get angry with men.
Yes, sir.
Was it "numbershot"?
I don't say "numbershot".
That's a little old-fashioned.
Maybe they don't say that either.
No way! Takeda Tensei said it all the time.
Shots! That's right.
Yeah... now the younger generation...
They don't say the number.
They say "nanshotto"...
It's "Nanchotteau.
Then say "Nanchotteau. Well, tell him Nanshot.
But what about Suitot?
What do you mean?
Tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk tsk.
What's Nanshot doing?
That's what I'm talking about.
What are you doing?
What are you doing right now? Like, "What are you doing?
Say it nicely.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And he's like, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Nanchot!
But what's a suitot?
How's that? That's it.
I want to be scolded.
Tsundere tsundere tsundere tsundere tsundere
Excuse me, may I?
Before Masai.
I love you guys.
Is that okay?
I love boys.
Yes, sir.
Then I'll go.
Yes, please.
Oh, my God. Nan shot.
But it's sweet.
Thank you so much. Thank you so much.
I'd give my heart to you. I'd give my heart to you.
I'm having a heart attack. I'm having a heart attack. I'm having a heart attack. My heart is pounding.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is kind of good. It's stacking up.
Right? Come on! There it is!
Here it comes!
Yes! Yeah!
Yes!
Boys love this kind of thing.
That's right, tsundere.
Tsundere.
A lot of boys are pissed off at girls.
That's true.
It's like they're always getting mad at me.
Like, "You're such a pussy!
If you say it in standard Japanese, it sounds like you're in a fight.
It's like they're really fighting.
But when you say it in dialect...
It's a little milder.
I love it.
Was I wrong?
Let's pull it back.
I'll make sure this is locked up tight.
I'll have it saved.
Oh, my God.
My, my, my!
No, really, then.
Are we done?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's just...
Aah! Where, where, where? Aah! Where, where, where?
You look beautiful right here.
It sure is.
Maybe they're pulling out now.
Some people have been waiting a long time.
That's right.
It's not an easy time to hear about a boy's water fugue, is it?
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
I don't want to hear it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's very satisfying.
Let's just...
Let's wrap it up.
Well, well, well, well.
See you next week.
See you next week for another live broadcast.
8:00 p.m.
Yes, the usual time and
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much for this week.
Master!
Ahh...
I'm getting so much feedback.
I wonder if the comments have stopped.
Maybe it's a flat tire or something, but it's not moving at all.
I can't get it to move at all.